Good to see you guys. Good to see you
yesterday at the at the mixer. Nice
little mixer. Um, happy to take your
questions.
>> What was your reaction?
>> Yeah, I'm not too surprised. You know, I
think um
I think he pondered it, you know, like
he said midway through the season and uh
you know, the cool thing is is he's one
of the best to ever call it and yet he's
going to let this young upandcomer and
that just shows you how much he believes
in Davis. Yeah.
>> How do you feel about on saying that uh
he's going to bat for you to get an
extension and is that your hope to get
an extension?
>> Oh yeah. I mean we're just we're so
busy, you know, this time of year and
and the season went longer, which is
cool, but the offseason gets condensed
and so we've been we've been rolling. Um
I mean that's really cool. It's not, you
know, it'll happen when it happens. I'm
not too worried about it. We got a lot
going on this offseason. Have a busy
offseason.
>> Yeah, we interviewed him and he he blew
out the interview. Sean and I and a few
other coaches were in there.
and uh just the detail u the football
knowledge you know he had never never
coached but obviously son of a coach and
and played and um he kind of blew us
away and then uh and then we're like
okay you know we'll give you a call in a
few days and and Sean and I are sitting
there and like 15 minutes later it's
like what the hell are we doing we
better get this guy back here he's going
to be gone you know if he has another
interview so just a lot of that and then
you know he's he's uh you know just the
relationship he has with these
quarterbacks the way they've all kind of
taken off and uh the connection with the
quarterback room, but the entire offense
and really the defense. Um he's a lot of
confidence as you know um you know
really confident for a guy who's 31
years old and we interviewed him. He's
what 28 if you do the math but um I'm
not sure I've seen the confidence for a
young coach like that and so you know
he's got a little swag to him. I think
the players appreciate it.
>> Oh yeah. I mean I would think I don't
know. I mean everyone's different. All
quarterbacks are different. He's got
that he he's got that juice, you know,
and he's got um I'm not going to say
cocky, but highly confident in in his
ability. And I'm sure that's from, you
know, playing at a young age.
>> Will that allow him to be comfortable
with looking over?
>> These guys have a great relationship.
This is this is three years they've been
together and they're all involved in the
game plan, all these coaches and and uh
so they have a really good relationship
and and I think it'll work. It'll work
great. You know, like I said, the good
news you have one of the best who's ever
called it who's going to be right there
and and during a game that, you know,
different coach, you know, it's not just
one guy all the time. So,
>> yeah,
>> we do. We do. I mean, he's still a pet.
I thought he had a really good year for
a rookie and and everything that was
thrown to him and then you know Dobbins
gets hurt and he comes in and and uh he
can just do you know he's dynamic with
the ball in the hands and you saw it at
all stages during the season big games
you know Jacksonville Buffalo play you
know just him with the ball in the hands
uh his hands his route running ability
uh I thought he improved first and
second down you know the game slowed
down for him as the season went on
couldn't be more happy about RJ
Yeah.
>> Hey, Johnny. Um,
you know, I think um it's a good
question. I mean, I I thought, you know,
I saw that. I think it's um
you know, maybe they just want to be
more efficient. You know, it would be
kind of cool to be home and just
watching tape and grinding, yet it it's
some, you know, the reason you want to
come here is just to get in front of the
players and get to know the players.
It's another step in the process of
trying to get to know these players. um
in person um face to face. You know, the
more you get to know these players, I
just think the better decisions you'll
make. Those those teams are really
sharp, you know, whatever they it be
good to talk to them. I haven't talked
to those guys, but um yeah, teaches
>> all
Yeah, really important. I mean, it's
credit to Richard T and Robert Simpson.
I mean, we've done, you know, I think
we've done 10 extensions in 18 months,
six maybe since August, you know, 400
million. Just think if we didn't get
those guys wrapped up, you know, what
we'd be facing. And, uh, every
offseason's a little like, wow, how we
going to fe, you know, but if we didn't
have all those guys done, just think how
more daunting the offseason would be.
So, really important to get ahead of it.
Um, all those players, I mean, there's
some all a lot of all pros, pro bowl, I
mean, there's a lot of good players in
that list. And so, um, we're identifying
the right players, the right makeup, you
know, the right people.
>> Yeah.
Does that how much does that inform like
whether you're drafting a guy early? Do
you think there are linebackers in this
class that that can play right away?
>> Yeah, I I think so. I think this is a
pretty good linebacker class. I mean, it
is a tough position for a rookie to come
in and play right away, especially with
some of the things we do and and but um
yeah, I do like the depth of this class.
I do. Um, and so we'll see. Again, it's
early in the process. We interviewed
those guys last night. It was a sharp
sharp group. Definitely.
>> Yeah. I mean, those those like Alex and
Justin, I mean, those guys are We'd love
to have those guys back. We'd love to
have them back. I mean, those regardless
of what's in the draft, these are guy,
you know, we see those guys as Broncos.
Um, you know, if we let those guys
leave, what do we do? you know, those
are good dudes. Now, it doesn't mean we
can get them, right? I mean, everyone's
watching tape, but um yeah, you look at
both. I mean, when you're you're getting
your plan for free agency, you look at
the draft, where's it strong there?
Okay, maybe it's it's strong, you know,
at receiver, maybe, you know, so it's
just it is a balance and and you do
develop your plan. So, it is a good
question. Um, but with those some
players, man, you just want to get back
regardless of of the strength, you know.
>> How do you balance whether you want to
go more on offense or defense? I mean,
obviously your defenses were very
strong. How do you balance that?
>> I think you just you have your meetings
like we've had and and you develop the
musts and Sean talks about the musts and
and like you have to get those filled
with good players. And so those are the
ones you attack. Offense, defense,
special team. We have musts for all
three phases. And so those you just have
to fill. I mean, it doesn't mean free
agency. I mean, it doesn't always mean
the draft. We got Jake JK Dobbins in I
don't know, May or something. June.
Yeah. So, you're always looking. I mean,
it never stops and there's, you know,
there's always something out there that,
you know, hopefully can help you.
>> Is it different that you're on the
doorstep of Super Bowl? Does that change
more because of how
>> I think we're we're always urgent and
again the season, man, you reset. You
reset, our team's not going to be the
same. So, we have to be urgent and we
don't know, we don't control a lot in
free agency. the guys could leave. And
so, um, you know, I think I said in
January, we're going to be urgent. We'll
be aggressive in our approach. No stone
unturned. We're looking at everything.
And then yet, you know, you have to be
measured and selective and make the
right decisions. You can't just go
crazy. Um, just because you you you
became, you know, three points, you
know, four point, whatever the Super
Bowl. But, uh, we'll be aggressive in
the approach, but really measured and
and try to make sound decisions. Even
though
you didn't push him for more time
at bay. How do you see this working out?
>> I mean I think it's a great problem to
have Mike really good problem to have. I
thought Jade took big steps. I mean we I
mean he you know Certan gets hurt. He
goes in and plays a major role and we
win I think all three g whatever two
games. I can't remember. Um he's right
on track. You know Jaquin had a a great
year. You know, our secondary had a
really, you know, it's Moss and Certan
and and we love the depth. I think it's
a great problem to have and and uh today
he's just going to keep getting better
and better. Really talented.
We'll see. I mean, we'll see what we do
with them. We're still working through
that. Um, I we want them here. I mean,
you know, certainly a team could a team
could call us. Who knows? Um, he's one
of our he's one of our core players. You
know, we we love we love having him
here.
>> No, go ahead.
>> You guys have been really good on the
offensive line without a lot of early
draft.
So what yeah how do you sort of balance
that when you have guys contract you
have such good foundation
>> I think you always have to look at your
offense and defensive lines but
offensive line you know what's the age
you don't want to age at the same time
um minor to what we took in the third
maybe foresight not sure who else we
drafted we we were fortunate to hit uh
we got Paulo as a free agent and then
the next year we got um Crumb and so you
dig through it you know our coaches uh
Strife and them do a great job of of of
evaluating these players. I think you
always have to feed the offensive line
and the defensive line, you know, to
sustain success in this league. And so
we'll continue to do that regardless,
you know, of how good our offensive line
is.
>> Yeah, really surprised. I think we all
felt like Vance would get a job. Um, we
love having him. I mean, he's a special
leader. Um, he's a great balance with
Shawn. um feel like Oliver, you know,
you can bring in a young player. Um what
he's done with Nick Bonito and just look
at all the young players certain all
these guys who've developed and and
under uh VJ's watch. He has such a great
presence to him and again we're um I
think he should be a head coach in this
league. I'm really fortunate that he's
that he's here.
>> PCO.
>> Yeah, I mean he never played in the left
side in his career as far as I know. I
don't think even Illinois. So, it's a
credit to him. I mean, he's big, he's
smart, he's really tough, and it didn't
always look pretty, but he played he
played well. And so, I mean, that's just
an added bonus. I mean, he played well
at right tackle when he had to start
there, you know, when Mack was out. And
so, again, young developmental player
who's kind of hit his stride and we're
we're fortunate to have him. when you
look
back on
what was the assessment of those.
>> Yeah,
>> I think we were really glad they were
both here. You know, Dre tone setter
obviously didn't play what he 10 games
maybe, but when he played he had an
impact. Um, when you bring in guys like
Green Law, Hufonga to a a really good
defense, it just took us to the next
level. And when Dre played, I felt like
he did that. Um, and Evan as well. I
mean, look at the big plays Evan made
throughout the season. had 50 catches. I
mean, you know, and and uh worked hard.
What do he play? I think he missed one
game, so maybe he played 18 games. And
and uh and so I was proud how those
guys, you know, how they worked. Yeah.